[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Jethro Tull invent in 1701, while he was living in Crowmarsh Gifford, a village in Oxfordshire, England?", "correct_answer": "The seed drill", "incorrect_answers": ["The combine machine", "The telescope", "The first modern rifle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This force prevents anything from escaping black holes.", "correct_answer": "Gravity force", "incorrect_answers": ["Centripetal force", "Nuclear force", "Centrifugal force"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the ice-skating girl in the movie For Your Eyes Only, who has a crush on James Bond?", "correct_answer": "Bibi Dahl", "incorrect_answers": ["Mimi Dahl", "Kiki Dahl", "Fifi Dahl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the chieftain, who in 1816, after the death of his father, seized power over the insignificant Zulu clan and transformed it into a nation?", "correct_answer": "Shaka", "incorrect_answers": ["Dingiswayo", "Senzangakhona", "Impis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is listed as the richest person in the world on the 2009 Forbes list?", "correct_answer": "Bill Gates", "incorrect_answers": ["Carlos Slim Helu", "Lawrence Ellison", "Warren  Buffett"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the diet of the Eastern Tiger Salamander mainly consist of?", "correct_answer": "Insects", "incorrect_answers": ["Shrimp", "Leaves", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This short in stature actor played one of the Bollard brothers, who was killed by the protagonist, Richard Malone, in the barbershop.", "correct_answer": "Tracy Walter", "incorrect_answers": ["Brookes Gardner", "Dennis Burkley", "Duncan Fraser"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As we learn during a meeting of S.P.E.C.T.R.E. agents, this is the villains codename in James Bonds, Thunderball.", "correct_answer": "Number 2", "incorrect_answers": ["Number 5", "Number 1", "Number 6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of oil is used for the preparation of the bread variety called Tiger bread?", "correct_answer": "Sesame oil", "incorrect_answers": ["Olive oil", "Almond oil", "Palm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What historical object was Indiana Jones father searching for his whole life?", "correct_answer": "The Holy Grail", "incorrect_answers": ["Noahs Ark", "A piece of the True Cross", "The Ark of the Covenant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie, released in 2000, won 5 Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Gladiator", "incorrect_answers": ["Memento", "Requiem for a Dream", "Traffic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following areas of the body is not considered a tender point in the diagnosis of fibromyalgya?", "correct_answer": "Ankles", "incorrect_answers": ["Knees", "Shoulder Blades", "Hips"]}]